allsales.guru 2017-06-06

# Privacy Policy

### Privacy Policy

This privacy policy adjusts the way how AllSales collects, uses, keeps and discloses information collected from users of the the Website "www.AllSales.su". This Privacy Policy relates to the Website www.AllSales.guru, all products and services offered by the AllSales.

### Personal information

We may collect personally information depend on activities, services, capabilities or resources that we provide on our website. Users can visit our site anonymously. We will not collect personally identifiable information from users only if they voluntarily provide such information to us. Users can always refuse to provide information.

### Publicly available information

We may collect identifying information publicly available about users when they visit AllSales Website, including the name of the browser, type of computer and technical information on our Website, for example, the type and version of the operating system, screen resolution and other similar information.

### Web browser. Cookies

Our website may use "Cookies" to provide better service. The web browser places cookies on the user's hard drive in order to account and track information about them.

### How we use the collected information

AllSales may collect and use non-personally not personal information for the following purposes:

  * To improve customer service. The information you provide will help us to respond to your requests and support needs more efficiently. 
  * In order to improve our site. We can use the feedback that you provide to improve our products and services. 
  * To launch promo, contests or other site functions. To send information that can be interesting for users. 
  * To send periodic e-mails, but only with personal consent of the user. Also user can easily unsubscribe from e-mailing. If the user decide to abandon a mailing list, he will receive emails that may include company news, updates, service information, etc. Anytime the user cans to unsubscribe from e-mailing (unsubscribe mechanism at the bottom of each email). 

### How we protect your information

We adopt appropriate measures to protect your personal information and data stored on our website from unauthorized access, alteration, disclosure or destruction.

### Sharing of personal information

We do not sell this information to third parties. We may share aggregated demographic information that not connected with any personal information about visitors and users with our business partners and advertisers for the purposes described above. We may resort to using third-party tools providers to help us with the analysis of site data or administration activities on our behalf, such as sending information bulletin or research. We can share information with these third parties for those limitedpurposes in case you gave us your permission.

### Third-party websites

Users may find advertising or other content on our website, as well as links to the sites and services of our partners, suppliers, advertisers, sponsors, licensors and others. We do not control the content or links that appear on these sites and do not response for their work related or not with our site. Furthermore, these websites or services, including their contents and links can always change. These sites and services may have their own privacy policies and customer service policies.

### Changes in Privacy Policy

AllSales has the discretion to update this privacy policy at any time. Each time, we will notify of changes in policy on the home page of our website. We recommend users to check this page for any changes. Your use of the Website after changes in this policy will be considered as your acceptance of those changes.

### Contact Us

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this site or your dealings with this site, please contact us: mail@AllSales.guru
